Guide to the Erasmus Hall Records 1325–1989 (bulk circa 1775–1975) MS 201
New-York Historical Society
- "Archives of Erasmus Hall High School"
  - Erasmus Hall High School—175th anniversary of charter (1962)
    - [Programs, article], 1962 (Offsite-box RC-1, Folder Erasmus Hall High School—175th Anniversary, 1787–1962)
      • Programs of the Civic Night and Education Night Exercises (May 9–10, 1962)
    - Engraved invitation to the 175th anniversary celebration, 1962 May 10 (Offsite-box RC-8a, Folder EHHS—175th anniv.—box of invitations)
      Box containing about 90 copies.
    - Erasmus Hall High School—One Hundred Seventy-Fifth Anniversary, 1962 (Offsite-box MS-26)
  - Erasmus Hall High School—200th anniversary of charter (1987)
    - Invitation, 1987 (Offsite-box RC-1, Folder EHHS—200th Anniversary, 1987)
  - Erasmus Hall High School—Alumni
    - Clippings, letters, memoranda, etc., regarding prominent students and alumni of Erasmus Hall High School, undated (Offsite-box RC-12, Folder EHHS—Alumni)
  - Erasmus Hall High School—Annual Reports
    - "Yearly Report"; notebook kept by Kate Turner, Asst. Principal, of attendance statistics, 1897–1905 (Offsite-box RC-2, Folder EHHS—Annual Reports, ca. 1897–1907)
    - Annual reports, all signed by Walter B. Gunnison, which were prepared for the State or City, 1897–1907 (Offsite-box RC-2, Folder EHHS—Annual Reports, ca. 1897–1907)
      The years indicated are for the year ending ____; the "C" and "S" references indicate whether the report is for the City or State:
      • 1897 (S, C)
      • 1898 (S, C)
      • 1899 (S)
      • 1900 (S)
      • 1901 (S, C)
      • 1902 (S)
      • 1903 (S)
      • 1904 (S)
      • 1905 (S)
      • 1907 (S)
  - Erasmus Hall High School—Application Blank
    - Original application blank for Erasmus Hall High School, 1896 (Offsite-box RC-2, Folder EHHS—Application blank & Courses of study, 1896)
  - Erasmus Hall High School—Athletics
    - [Programs, newspaper clippings, publications, etc.], 1904–1938 (Offsite-box RC-9a, Folder EHHS—Athletics [2 folders])
      • Printed programs, newspaper clippings, etc., about athletic meets, track meets, football games, etc.
      • Also, copies of Sports Review, 1936–8.
      • Also, scrapbook of athletic material, 1907–10. Also, 1904 calendar with photos of EHHS athletic teams.
    - Photographs of teams, games, etc., circa 1900–circa 1975 (Offsite-box RC-9b, Folder EHHS—Athletics—Photos [2 folders])
  - Erasmus Hall High School—Awards, Medals, etc.
    - Miscellaneous awards and certificates, undated (Offsite-box RC-3a, Folder EHHS—Awards—misc. (folder 2))
  - Erasmus Hall High School—Banners
    - Large rolled banner with hand-painted portrait of Erasmus, and dates 1787–1911 (Offsite-box RC-5c (tube))
    - Two felt banners for Erasmus Hall, undated [circa 1940s] (Offsite-box RC-10a, Folder EHHS—Felt banners)
  - Erasmus Hall High School—Bedford Avenue wing
    - Six photographs showing construction of Bedford Ave. wing, circa 1925 (Offsite-box RC-3a, Folder EHHS—Bedford Ave. wing)
  - Erasmus Hall High School—Biology Department
    - Minutes of the Meetings of the Biology Department, Feb. 6, 1907 to Dec. 19, 1911, 1907–1911 (Offsite-box RC-3b, Volume Science Section)
      Pages 1 to 46 taken from a notebook.
      Inside cover of hardcover notebook containing minutes of "Science Section."
    - "Laboratory Experiments, Biology, Erasmus Hall High School, Edition of 1962–63", 1962–1963 (Offsite-box RC-3a, Folder EHHS—Chemistry Dep't., Biology Dep't.)
  - Erasmus Hall High School—Board of Education Centennial Pageant (1942)
    - Material relating to the centennial celebration of the Board of Education, held at Erasmus Hall High School, 1942 April 15–16 (Offsite-box RC-8a, Folder EHHS—Board of Education Centennial Pageant (1942))
  - Erasmus Hall High School—Bookmarks
    - Bookmarks with profile of Erasmus and "EHHS" monogram, undated (Offsite-box RC-1, Folder EHHS—Bookplate (1930) and Bookmarks)
  - Erasmus Hall High School—Bookplate
    - Bookplate designed by A. J. Grodin, Class of 1930, showing a stylized aerial view of the grounds of Erasmus Hall High School (Offsite-box RC-1, Folder EHHS—Bookplate (1930) and Bookmarks)
  - Erasmus Hall High School—Chapel
    - Correspondence relating to organ in chapel of Erasmus Hall High School, 1915–1918 (Offsite-box RC-2, Folder EHHS Chapel—Coats of Arms, Organ, etc.)
  - Erasmus Hall High School—Chapel—Coats of Arms
    - [List of shields], undated (Offsite-box RC-2, Folder EHHS Chapel—Coats of Arms, Organ, etc.)
      Early in the administration of Dr. John F. McNeill (EHHS principal), the carved shield designs in the school chapel were embellished with hand-painted coats of arms of the founding families of Erasmus Hall Academy. This folder contains lists of the shields.
      Photographs showing the chapel at the time these shields existed, can be found under: Erasmus Hall High School—Views.
  - Erasmus Hall High School—Chemistry Department
    - Chemistry Experiments (for use in EHHS), 1941?, 1956 (Offsite-box RC-3a, Folder EHHS—Chemistry Dep't., Biology Dep't.)
      Two editions: n.d. (1941?), 1956.
  - Erasmus Hall High School—Christmas Concert
    - Literature and printed programs for the annual Erasmus Hall Christmas Concert [incomplete], 1947–1975 (Offsite-box RC-4a, Folder EHHS—Christmas Concert)
    - "Erasmus Hall High School Presents its Annual Christmas Concert" [33-1/3 LP record album], 1965 December 23 (Offsite-box RC-4b, Folder Recording of EHHS Christmas Concert)
  - Erasmus Hall High School—Church Avenue Wing
    - [Transcript of remarks at dedication], 1912 October 10 (Offsite-box RC-1, Folder Erasmus Hall High School—One Hundred Twenty-fifth Anniversary (1912))
      The Church Avenue wing was dedicated Oct. 10, 1912, in conjunction with the celebration of the school's 125th anniversary. A transcript of the speakers' remarks at the dedication, and material relating generally to the anniversary celebration.
  - Erasmus Hall High School—Class Day Programs
    - Class Day Programs, 1897–1960 (Offsite-box RC-4a, Folder EHHS—Class Day Programs)
      Programs for the following years are available:
      • 1897
      • 1898
      • 1900 [17 copies]
      • 1901
      • 1910
      • 1911
      • 1912
      • 1913 [ticket and dance book only]
      • 1914
      • 1915
      • 1916
      • 1917
      • 1918
      • 1919
      • 1921
      • 1922
      • 1925
      • 1934
      • 1937
      • 1938
      • 1940 [3 copies]
      • 1941 [2 copies]
      • 1945
      • 1947
      • 1949
      • 1951
      • 1959 [3 copies]
      • 1960
  - Erasmus Hall High School—Commencement (1900, 1901)
    - Original programs for graduating exercises for the classes of 1900 and 1901, 1900, 1901 (Offsite-box RC-2, Folder Graduation Programs for EHHS, 1900, 1901)
      These were the first and second graduating classes of Erasmus Hall High School.
  - Erasmus Hall High School—Commencement (1902–1929)
    - Programs of the Graduating Exercises of the Classes of 1902 to 1929, 1902–1929 (Offsite-box RC-3a, Folder Programs of Graduating Exercises of EHHS, 1902–1929)
      Mounted in notebook without covers.
  - Erasmus Hall High School—Commencement (1905)
    - "Erasmus Gala Night at Majestic Theatre. The Largest Class Ever Graduated From Old Erasmus Hall," Brooklyn Daily Eagle, 1905 June 24 (Offsite-box RC-2, Folder EHHS—Cornerstone Laying)
      Lists all of the graduates and award winners.
      Gift of Dr. Henry E. Meleney, class of 1905.
  - Erasmus Hall High School—Commencement (1923–date [1974])
    - Commencement programs, 1923–1974 (Offsite-box RC-11, Folder EHHS Graduation Programs)
      Programs for the following years are available (for the June class unless otherwise specified):
      • 1923 (Jan.)
      • 1934 [2 copies]
      • 1936
      • 1938 (Jan. & June)
      • 1939 (Jan. & June)
      • 1940 (Jan. & June)
      • 1941 (Jan. & June)
      • 1942 (Jan. & June)
      • 1943 (Jan. & June)
      • 1944 (Jan. & June)
      • 1945 (Jan. & June)
      • 1946 (Feb. & June)
      • 1947 (Feb. & June)
      • 1948 (Feb. & June)
      • 1950 (Jan. & June)
      • 1951 (Jan. & June)
      • 1952 (Jan.)
      • 1953 (Jan.)
      • 1954
      • 1955 (Jan. & June)
      • 1956 (Jan. & June)
      • 1957
      • 1963
      • 1967 (Jan. & June)
      • 1968
      • 1972
      • 1973
  - Erasmus Hall High School—Concerts
    - Programs for various concerts, 1909–1979 (Offsite-box RC-4a, Folder EHHS—Concerts)
      See also Erasmus Hall High School—Christmas Concert
      See also Erasmus Hall High School—Spring Concert
      See also Erasmus Hall High School—Sing
  - Erasmus Hall High School—Cornerstone Laying (1905)
    - [Program and newspaper clipping], 1905 January 17 (Offsite-box RC-2, Folder EHHS—Cornerstone Laying)
      • "Cornerstone of the New Erasmus Hall High School Laid To-Day." Brooklyn Daily Eagle, Jan. 17, 1905, p. 1. Accompanied by letter from Dr. Henry E. Meleney, who donated this clipping and one regarding the 1905 graduation.
      • Program of the laying of the cornerstone, Jan. 17, 1905 (2 copies).
    - [Photograph], 1905 January 17 (Offsite-box RC-2, Folder EHHS—Cornerstone Laying)
      Original glass plate negative, 5 x 7", of the laying of the cornerstone of Erasmus Hall High School, Jan. 17, 1905. Negative made by Mr. Edmund Bramhill Child, and presented to the school in October, 1937. Also present is a 5 x 7" print from the negative.
      Note: a second negative taken by Mr. Child, but not as good, is in the collections of the New-York Historical Society.
    - Original trowel used in laying cornerstone of Erasmus Hall High School [NOT PRESENT], [1905 January 17] (Box [unknown])
      Original trowel used in laying cornerstone of Erasmus Hall High School, Jan. 1905.
      It is inscribed as follows: "Used in laying the cornerstone of the new Erasmus Hall High School January seventeenth Nineteen hundred and five by Hon. George W. Schaedle, Member of the Committee on Buildings, Board of Education, and by him presented as a momento [sic] to the school. John Thatcher & Sons, Builders."
    - Silver medallion issued in 1905 to commemorate laying of the cornerstone of the new building of Erasmus Hall High School [NOT PRESENT], [1905 January 17] (Box [unknown])
      This medal is engraved with the name of Clarence E. Meleney. In original leather presentation box. Received as a gift from G. C. Meleney, White Plains, N.Y., June 1975.
  - Erasmus Hall High School—Courses of Study
    - "Courses of Study Adopted for the Erasmus Hall High School", [1896 September] (Offsite-box RC-2, Folder EHHS—Application blank & Courses of study, 1896)
      Undated, but as this is "for use during the first term of the new school," the date is September 1896. [8 copies]
    - Requirements for Graduation from High Schools... for the year 1912. Department of Education, City of New York. (Offsite-box RC-11, Folder Board of Education, Misc. Publications)
    - Courses of Study in Erasmus Hall High School, 1948 February (Offsite-box RC-2, Folder EHHS—Courses of Study, 1948)
  - Erasmus Hall High School—Diploma
    - [Diploma awarded to Ruth M. Dunham], 1913 June 26 (Offsite-box RC-5b)
      "Diploma of Graduation: This DIPLOMA is awarded to Ruth M. Dunham Who has completed the Regular Course of 4 years in the Erasmus Hall High School and has satisfactorily passed all examinations required for graduation, June 26, 1913. (Signed)... W. B. Gunnison, Principal." 14 x 17"
  - Erasmus Hall High School—English Department
    - Erasmus Hall High School English Handbook, 1921, 1937, undated (Offsite-box RC-3a, Folder English Department Handbooks)
      Three different editions, n.d., but all issued under chairmanship of A. Barnett Langdale.
      Folder also includes two pamphlets:
      • William E. McVey, Minimal Essentials in Manners and Right Conduct for High School Students (1921)
      • Phil B. Noah, Charting Success by the Five Pointed Star: Suggestions for High School Students (1937)
  - Erasmus Hall High School—Faculty
    - Miscellaneous photos, clippings, etc. relating to various members of the faculty, undated (Offsite-box RC-14a, Folder Erasmus Hall High School—Faculty (Misc.))
    - "Report of Local Committee to Committee on Teachers," Erasmus Hall High School, 1900 June 30 (Offsite-box RC-14a, Folder Erasmus Hall High School—Faculty (Misc.))
      Lists the complete faculty for the year beginning Sept. 1900 [1899?].
    - [Faculty performance ratings], 1896–1906 (Offsite-box RC-14a, Folder EHHS—Faculty ratings, 1896–1906)
      Ledger book in which each faculty member was rated for performance. Every teacher hired during the first ten years of the school's existence as a public high school is rated.
    - Notebooks listing teachers and classes taught, 1896–1912 (Offsite-box RC-14a, Folder EHHS—Organization 1896–1912 Lists of Teachers)
      Recorded by the Erasmus Hall Organization.
    - Gray binder with teachers' daily programs, 1898–1924 (Offsite-box RC-14b, Volume Erasmus Hall High School Teachers' Daily Programs)
    - Loyalty pledge taken by faculty of Erasmus Hall High School, 1917, 1921 (Offsite-box RC-2, Folder EHHS—Loyalty Pledge | EHHS—Named as Communist breeding ground)
      Loyalty pledge taken by faculty of Erasmus Hall High School pursuant to a state law passed during the post-World War I "Red Scare." Also, material relating to loyalty dated 1917.
    - "To John F. McNeill: An Appreciation", circa 1934 (Offsite-box RC-2, Folder Dr. John F. McNeill, principal of EHHS, 1934–65 (2 folders))
      Book presented to John F. McNeill with the signatures of every member of the faculty, according to department.
    - [Lists of faculty], undated (Offsite-box RC-9b, Folder EHHS—Faculty—1912)
      Two envelopes labeled:
      • "Small photos with names on back—EHHS Print—Paul's list!"
      • "List of Faculty made by: A. S. Cameron from Paul's very bad list!!!"
      The list by Ms. Alex Cameron corresponds to the copy of the "Long photograph of the complete faculty [numbered copy 2]" taken on campus at the time of the 125th anniversary celebration, 1912. See oversize folder 1.2.
  - Erasmus Hall High School—Faculty Dinners
    - Programs, bills, and notes concerning the Faculty Dinners of Erasmus Hall, 1898–1967 (Offsite-box RC-14a, Folder EHHS—Faculty Dinners (2 folders))
      Programs are available for the following years:
      • 1898 (first)
      • 1900 (Jan.)
      • 1900 (Dec.)
      • 1902 (Jan.)
      • 1902 (Dec.)
      • 1904
      • 1905
      • 1906
      • 1907
      • 1909
      • 1920
      • 1931
      • 1932
      • 1933
      • 1967
  - Erasmus Hall High School—Faculty Plays
    - [Faculty play programs], 1926, 1931 (Offsite-box RC-4a, Folder EHHS—Faculty Plays)
      • Faculty Play, Mar. 26–27, 1926 [4 copies]
      • Faculty Play, Apr. 17–18, 1931 [5 copies]
  - Erasmus Hall High School—Faculty—Photographs
    - [Faculty photographs], undated (Offsite-box RC-14a, Folder EHHS Faculty Photographs)
    - Long photograph of the complete faculty [numbered copy 1], 1912 (Oversize large, Folder 1.1)
      Taken on campus at time of 125th anniversary celebration.
      Formerly framed (frame discarded 2021), with only accurate identification of faculty members.
    - Long photograph of the complete faculty [numbered copy 2], 1912 (Oversize large, Folder 1.2)
      Taken on campus at time of 125th anniversary celebration. This numbered copy was presented in Dec. 1972 by Ms. Alex Cameron, a teacher who appears in the photo. Poor condition (split in half).
      For Cameron's list identifiying the teachers in the photograph, see Box 9a, Folder "EHHS—Faculty—1912."
    - Long photograph of the complete faculty [flat copies], 1912 (Oversize large, Folder 1.3)
      Taken on campus at time of 125th anniversary. Three copies (one complete, two partial).
    - Long photograph of the complete faculty [rolled copy], 1912 (Offsite-box RC-5a)
      Taken on campus at time of 125th anniversary celebration. Poor condition.
  - Erasmus Hall High School—Floor Plans
    - Floor plans on blueprint paper of the entire school (basement and four floors), circa 1930s (Offsite-box RC-5b, Folder EHHS—Floor Plans)
      Not dated, but ca. 1930s, as the Snyder Ave. wing was not yet constructed. [3 copies]
    - Proposed Addition to Erasmus Hall High School. Walter C. Martin, arch't. Aug. 13, 1937 (rev. Sept. 16, 1937) (Offsite-box RC-5b, Folder Snyder Av. Wing blueprints)
      This is an 8 page blueprint of Snyder Avenue wing.
    - Floor plans on blueprint paper of the entire school (basement and five floors), circa 1940 (Offsite-box RC-5a, Folder EHHS—Floor plans)
      Not dated, but ca. 1940, as the Snyder Avenue wing is present and referred to as the "new addition."
  - Erasmus Hall High School—General Organization
    - Constitution and other material relating to the General Organization, undated (Offsite-box RC-4a, Folder EHHS—General Organization (G.O.))
  - Erasmus Hall High School—Grade Advisors
    - [Printed notices], circa 1914–1917, undated (Offsite-box RC-2, Folder EHHS—Grade Advisors)
      • Printed notice of welcome to Erasmus Hall freshmen, signed by Emilie L. Platt, Grade Advisor, n.d., but World War I era.
      • Printed notice of welcome, similar to above, but signed Charles M. Stebbins, n.d.
      • Printed notice of consolation to students who failed first semester's work, signed Charles M. Stebbins, n.d.
  - Erasmus Hall High School—Guide
    - Erasmus Hall Handbook / Guide / Answer Book, 1915–1978 (Offsite-box RC-11, Folder Erasmus Hall H. S.—Guide)
      The following editions are available, with variant titles as indicated:
      • Erasmus Hall Handbook 1915
      • Erasmus Hall Handbook 1932 [6th ed.]
      • G. O. Handbook Feb. 1937
      • G. O Handbook Fall 1937 [4 copies]
      • G. O. Handbook Spring 1938
      • The Handbook Fall 1938
      • The Handbook Spring 1939 [2 copies]
      • The Handbook Fall 1939 [3 copies]
      • The Handbook Spring 1940 [2 copies]
      • The Handbook Fall 1940 [2 copies]
      • G. O. Handbook Fall 1941
      • G. O. Handbook Fall 1942 [3 copies]
      • General Organization Handbook Spring 1943 [2 copies]
      • G. O. Handbook Spring 1943 [2 copies]
      • G. O. Handbook Spring 1944
      • G. O. Handbook Fall 1944 [3 copies]
      • G. O. Handbook Spring 1945 [3 copies]
      • G. O. Handbook Fall 1945 [3 copies]
      • The Handbook Spring 1946 [3 copies]
      • The Handbook Spring [sic; Fall] 1946 [3 copies]
      • The Handbook Spring 1947 [2 copies]
      Erasmus Hall Guide. Published by the Faculty of Erasmus Hall High School for the Students.
      • v. 1 Jan. 1948 [3 copies]
      • v. 2 Sept. 1950 [3 copies]
      • v. 3 Sept. 1959 [2 copies]
      • v. 4 Sept. 1966 [4 copies]
      • Sept. 1978
      Answer Book for New Erasmians, publd. by G. O.
      • v. 1–3 (1956–59) [2 copies]
  - Erasmus Hall High School—History
    - Newspaper clippings regarding plans for destroying or moving Academy, and, finally, plans to restore it, undated (Offsite-box RC-1, Folder Erasmus Hall Academy—History)
  - Erasmus Hall High School—History (1896)
    - [Program, tickets, newspaper clippings], 1896 October 14 (Offsite-box RC-1, Folder Transfer of Erasmus Hall Academy to the City of Brooklyn, 1896 (original program, clippings))
      • Original program and tickets of admission for the formal transfer of the Academy to the City of Brooklyn for use as a public high school. Ceremony was held Oct. 14, 1896 at Flatbush Reformed Dutch Church.
    - Annual report of the Superintendent of Public Instruction to the Board of Education of the city of Brooklyn, 1896 (Offsite-box RC-11, Folder Annual Report... Board of Education...)
  - Erasmus Hall High School—History (1896–1899)
    - Minutes of the Meetings of the Local Committee appointed for the new high school to be established in Erasmus Hall, 1896–1899 (Offsite-box RC-12, Volume Minutes of the Local Committee...)
      Richard Young, Chairman, W. B. Gunnison, Secretary. Ledger notebook.
  - Erasmus Hall High School—History (1900–1904)
    - Clara A. Cummings Doolittle letters and scrapbooks regarding her years at Erasmus Hall, 1900–1904 (Offsite-box RC-3a, Folder Letters & Scrapbooks of Clara A. Cummings Doolittle)
  - Erasmus Hall High School—History (1902)
    - Petitions to the Board of Education for the erection of a new building for Erasmus Hall High School, [1902] (Offsite-box RC-12, Folder Petitions to the Board of Education...)
      More than 100 sheets tied together, each with signatures and addresses of both famous and obscure Brooklynites.
  - Erasmus Hall High School—History (1917–1921)
    - Loyalty pledge taken by faculty of Erasmus Hall High School in 1921, pursuant to a state law passed during the post-World War I "Red Scare", 1917, 1921 (Offsite-box RC-2, Folder EHHS—Loyalty Pledge | EHHS—Named as Communist breeding ground)
      Also, material relating to loyalty dated 1917.
  - Erasmus Hall High School—History (1941)
    - Clippings about "virus of communism" breeding in New York City schools, 1941 March (Offsite-box RC-2, Folder EHHS—Loyalty Pledge | EHHS—Named as Communist breeding ground)
      Erasmus Hall High School was named as one of the dozen schools involved:
      • "Reds in 3 Boro Schools Plot Against U.S., Probers Charge." Brooklyn Eagle, March 24, 1941.
      • "9 High Schools Called Centers of Red Activity," New York Herald Tribune, March --, 1941.
  - Erasmus Hall High School—History (1957–1963)
    - [Newspaper clippings and correspondence], undated (Offsite-box RC-12, Folder EHHS—History—1957–63)
      In 1957, a TIME Magazine survey named Erasmus Hall as one of the 38 outstanding high schools in the U.S. A Ladies' Home Journal survey in 1963 named EHHS as one of the top 25. These articles resulted in much publicity (newspaper articles, etc.) and correspondence (from high schools wishing to learn the secret of success).
  - Erasmus Hall High School—History (1964)
    - Flatbush, vol. 43, no. 12, 1964 December (Offsite-box RC-2, Folder Dr. John F. McNeill, principal of EHHS, 1934–65 (2 folders))
      Published by the Flatbush Chamber of Commerce, devoted to the history of Erasmus Hall High School. Also, includes article (p. 2) on Dr. John F. McNeill being named "Man of the Year" by the Kiwanis Club of Prospect Park.
  - Erasmus Hall High School—Landmark Plaque Dedication (1958)
    - Correspondence, news clippings, and printed material relating to the landmark plaque placed on the old Academy building by the New York Community Trust, [1958 May 2] (Offsite-box RC-1, Folder EHHS—Landmark Plaque Dedication, 1958)
  - Erasmus Hall High School—Landmark Status
    - [Material relating to the landmark and national register status of the Academy Building], 1958, 1966, 1975 (Offsite-box RC-1, Folder EHHS—Landmark Status)
      A landmark plaque was placed on the old Academy building by the New York Community Trust on May 2, 1958. This private trust began marking important landmarks because there was no city agency to do so. Erasmus Hall Academy was declared an official city landmark on March 15, 1966 by the New York City Landmarks Preservation Commission (which did not come into being until 1965). In December 1975, Erasmus Hall Academy was entered in the National Register of Historic Places maintained by the U. S. Dept. of the Interior.
  - Erasmus Hall High School—Library
    - Miscellaneous clippings and photographs, undated (Offsite-box RC-5a, Folder Erasmus—Library—Clippings)
    - Photographs of both the "old" and "new" Erasmus Hall High School libraries, undated (Offsite-box RC-5a, Folder EHHS—Library)
      The former being what is now the Art Gallery / Student Lounge on the second floor of the Flatbush Arch.
  - Erasmus Hall High School—Library—Annual Reports